downloadrush.com 2012-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Files Provider

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

1\. We do not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.  
2\. We do not share your contact information with another User without your consent.  
3\. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology.

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal and other information we receive from Users of the FilesProvider Site. 

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time and will handle your information in accordance with the version that was in place when you submitted it. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the home page of the Site. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use. By continuing to use the FilesProvider service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the FilesProvider Site, you are consenting to the changes. 

The purpose of the FilesProvider Site is to provide its Users with an infrastructure which enables the Users to download files from the most popular hosting websites by usage of one FilesProvider account. FilesProvider links its Users with the file-sharing and torrent networks. None of the torrent files, peers or content is controlled by FilesProvider administrators or servers. The same applies to the filesharing networks. None of the files stored remotely, nor the users that have uploaded them are controlled by FilesProvider administrators or servers. You willingly provide us certain personal information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the FilesProvider Site. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, you should not become a User of FilesProvider. 

### The FilesProvider Site and Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the FilesProvider Site. The Site may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by FilesProvider. FilesProvider has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party site. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party sites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release FilesProvider from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party site to which this Site may be linked. 

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Service, the Site and the related features, to administer your subscription and to enable Users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. Below are the types and categories of information that we collect. 

### Personal Information Collected

We collect your personal information in the following ways: 

**Registration**   
In order to become a User, you must first create an account on our Site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge is personal information allowing others, including FilesProvider, to identify you: email address and a password chosen by you. 

**Log Data**   
When you visit the Site or use the Service, whether as a FilesProvider subscriber or a non-registered User just browsing our servers automatically record information about your use of the Service and your visit to the Site ("Log Data"). The Log Data may include information such as your computers Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, what Software you were using, the web page you were visiting immediately prior to visiting our Site, pages of our Site that you visited, the time spent on those pages, information you searched for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Sites technical administration, to improve our Sites functionality and User-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors needs. We also use this information to verify that Users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests. 

**Cookies**

Like most Sites, FilesProvider uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows FilesProvider to recognize you as a User when you return to the FilesProvider Site using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use the FilesProvider Site. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on our Site. 

One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once you've logged in to your FilesProvider account. The next time you visit the FilesProvider Site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the service. 

Additionally, if you log out of the FilesProvider Site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the FilesProvider Site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. 

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing User preferences and tracking User trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the FilesProvider Site or services. FilesProvider does not store personally identifiable information in the cookies. 

### Web Beacons

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. 

To deliver these ads properly, FilesProvider may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by FilesProvider so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other sites. 

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other sites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. FilesProvider does not provide personally identifiable information to any advertiser or any other third party. 

### Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the FilesProvider Site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave FilesProvider. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the FilesProvider Service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law. 

### FilesProvider Communications

FilesProvider will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the FilesProvider Site or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging. If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access (including text messaging charges for messages to your mobile device). Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from FilesProvider related to the proper functioning of your account. You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into your "Account" and amending your email notification choices. By using the Site, especially by clicking "Create free FilesProvider account" during the registration process, you also agrees to receive commercial messages from FilesProvider in your email. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

FilesProvider takes the privacy of Users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill Users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and they are bound by confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. 

We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our Services to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on FilesProvider. 

### Teaming with Other Organizations to Offer Combined and Other Services

FilesProvider may offer our Services in connection with other sites (including updates about the FilesProvider Service) or may team with other online services to give you the combined results of both services or additional services and benefits. Platform Applications can be designed by Platform Developers or by a subset of Platform Developers with whom FilesProvider has more closely aligned ("Partners"). 

In the case of Partners, we do some vetting and we only work with trusted Partners. Because of FilesProvider's trust in these Partners, Platform Applications or services designed by a Partner may be automatically granted permission to access account information to provide the combined services. 

For Platform Applications designed by most Platform Developers, you will be asked to confirm acceptance of the Platform Developers' respective privacy policies and User agreements, which have not necessarily been reviewed or approved by FilesProvider. In these cases, it will be your choice whether or not to make use of the services and whether to proceed under the Platform Developers terms. 

Platform Developers are required to agree to restrictions on access, storage and usage of your information. However, while we typically enter into contractual agreements and take technical steps to restrict possible misuse of such information by such Platform Developers, we may not screen or approve Platform Developers, and we cannot and do not guarantee that all Platform Developers will abide by such restrictions and agreements. 

FilesProvider is not responsible for your use of or inability to use any Platform Applications, including the content, accuracy, or reliability of such applications and the privacy practices or other policies of Platform Developers. 

FilesProvider allows other companies to place advertisements on the Site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the Site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the Site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the Site generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means. 

### Legal Disclaimer

FilesProvider cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of FilesProvider or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

### Disclosures to others

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of a FilesProvider division or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell FilesProvider's assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us. 

### Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to FilesProvider. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. 

### Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated information that does not include personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal Information. 

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to "and maintained on" computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to such transfer. 

### Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other web sites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third partys web site. The fact that we link to a web site or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other web sites you visit. 

### Accessing and Changing your Account Information

You can review the information you provided us and make any desired changes to them, or to the settings for your FilesProvider account including your email at any time by logging in to your account on the FilesProvider Site. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, FilesProvider may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. We take your rights seriously and encourage you to use them if you deem this to be appropriate. You may exercise these rights by emailing us at privacy@filesprovider.com. 

### Deleting your Account

You can also delete your account through the FilesProvider Site. If you delete your FilesProvider account, we may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. In order to delete your account please visit "Delete Account" section associated with your account. 

### Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations imposed by applicable law and regulations: 

1\. You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties.   
2\. You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic. 

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by FilesProvider, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which our Users adhere to the FilesProvider Site and the services which it offers. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

FilesProvider may update this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

If you use the FilesProvider Service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. 

### Security

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable laws related to security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

### Data Retention Policy

FilesProvider may retain your account information indefinitely, regardless of whether you have disabled your account on the Site. FilesProvider will retain Log Data consistent with applicable legal requirements. Generally, at a minimum, FilesProvider will retain the Log Data collected from you in its active, internal company databases for six months, at which point it will migrate such Log Data to its offline archival systems, where FilesProvider will retain the Log Data for a period of three years (together, the "Retention Period"). After the Retention Period, FilesProvider will purge the Log Data from its systems. In the event of an investigation by law enforcement or a response to claims or legal process, we may retain the Log Data until such investigation or process is completed, which may be longer than the Retention Period. 

### How to contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please email us at support@filesprovider.com
